- Hello, Mommy, Daddy. How are you?
- Pretty good, can't complain.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Oh, I'm sure you can.
Just give it a minute.
(Raj:)Listen, uh...
(Raj:)There's something I want
to talk to you about.
(Raj:)I wasn't ready until now
but I think it's time.
(Dr Koothrappali:)It's finally happening.
(Dr Koothrappali:)You're coming out of the closet,
aren't you?
(Mrs Koothrappali:)We love you
and we accept your aIternate lifestyle.
Just keep it to yourseIf.
(Raj:)No, I'm not gay.
(Raj:)If anything, I'm metrosexual.
(Dr Koothrappali:)What's that?
(Raj:)It means I like women
as well as their skin-care products.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Well, if you're not coming out...
(Dr Koothrappali:)...why did you call us
during the cricket semi-finals?
(Raj:)I'm tired of trying to meet someone...
...and I think l'd like you
to help me find a...
(Raj:)A wife.
(Mrs Koothrappali:)And just to clarify, a female wife?